<?xml version="1.0"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"><channel><item><category>Accomodation</category><title>Contoso Hotel</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><pushpinURL>images/homeLocation.png</pushpinURL><shortDescription>Contemporary, sophisticated hotel situated in the heart of the city</shortDescription><longDescription>Contemporary, sophisticated hotel situated in the heart of the city</longDescription><addressLine1>1901 5th Ave</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA 98101</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Accomodation Hotel Room Bed Double Queen</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.612943</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.33794</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Music</category><title>Experience Music Project</title><imageURL>DemoImages/emp.jpg</imageURL><shortDescription>Experience Music Project (EMP) is dedicated to the exploration of creativity and innovation in popular music.</shortDescription><longDescription>Experience Music Project (EMP) is dedicated to the exploration of creativity and innovation in popular music. By blending interpretative, interactive exhibition with cutting-edge technology, EMP captures and reflects the essence of rock ‘n’ roll, its roots in jazz, soul, gospel, country and the blues, as well as rock’s influence on hip-hop, punk and other recent genres. Visitors can view rare artifacts and memorabilia and experience the creative process by listening to musicians tell their own stories.</longDescription><addressLine1>325 5th Ave N</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Music Museum</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.621068</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.347587</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>Space Needle</title><imageURL>DemoImages/spaceneedle.jpg</imageURL><shortDescription>The symbol of Seattle, and one of the most recognizable structures in the world.</shortDescription><longDescription>Built in 1962, the Space Needle served as the symbol of that year's World's Fair.  It has since become the symbol of Seattle, and one of the most recognizable structures in the world.  The privately owned Space Needle is managed by the Space Needle Corporation.</longDescription><addressLine1>400 Broad St</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Attraction Monument</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.6198</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.348809</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Food</category><title>The Pink Door</title><imageURL>DemoImages/pinkdoor.jpg</imageURL><shortDescription>The Pink Door tempts with homespun Italian-American food.</shortDescription><longDescription>The Pink Door tempts with homespun Italian-American food,conversation that flows liberally as the Baralo, provocative -always free- live entertainment, and a warm, lively respite from the ordinary world.</longDescription><addressLine1>1919 Post Alley</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Restaurant Eat Food Drink Entertainment</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.610127</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.342046</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Music</category><title>Dimitriou's Jazz Alley</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>Seattle jazz nightclub and restaurant.</shortDescription><longDescription>Seattle jazz nightclub and restaurant established in 1979.</longDescription><addressLine1>2033 6th Ave</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Restaurant Food Music Entertainment</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.614638</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.338732</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>Gas Works Park</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>Gas Works Park has a play area with a large play barn, and big hill popular for flying kites.</shortDescription><longDescription>Gas Works Park has a play area with a large play barn, and big hill popular for flying kites. Special park features include a sundial, and a beautiful view of Seattle. Burke-Gilman Trail runs past Gas Works parking lot and follows the Burlington-Northern Railroad 12.5 miles north to Kirkland Log Boom Park.</longDescription><addressLine1>2101 N Northlake Way</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Park Kite Fly Picnic</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.646862</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.333883</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>Westlake Center</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>Visit Westlake Center located in Seattle, Washington for the best in shopping, entertainment and dining!</shortDescription><longDescription>Visit Westlake Center located in Seattle, Washington for the best in shopping, entertainment and dining!</longDescription><addressLine1>400 Pine St</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Shopping Dinning Monorail Cafe</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.61118</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.337659</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>Banya</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>Banya5 is an urban spa and health facility which offers a unique blend of old world wellness rituals in a friendly contemporary environment.</shortDescription><longDescription>Banya 5 is an urban spa and health facility which offers a unique blend of old world wellness rituals in a friendly contemporary environment. A series of relaxing wet heat and dry heat experiences coupled with exhilarating pool plunges produce a vivid circulatory experience with numerous mental and physical health benefits. Banya 5 is an environment which promotes wellness, vitality and rejuvenation of the soul.</longDescription><addressLine1>217 9th Ave N</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Spa Relaxation Swim Massage</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.619901</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.339772</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Food</category><title>Agua Verde Cafe & Paddle Club</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>The Agua Verde paddle club and cafe offers kayak rentals and great Mexican food on the waterfront of Seattle, Washington.</shortDescription><longDescription>We offer creative, healthy Mexican food in a casual, waterfront setting. Sea kayaks are available for hourly rental downstairs. Paddle past eclectic floating homes with vistas of the Seattle skyline in the background.</longDescription><addressLine1>1303 NE Boat St</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Park Kayak Rental Food Cafe</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.651811</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.314539</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>REI</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>More than a store, we rank among the Emerald City's top sightseeing attractions.</shortDescription><longDescription>Serving Seattleites since 1944. More than a store, we rank among the Emerald City's top sightseeing attractions. Here you'll find the motherlode of gear—plus a mountain bike test trail, gear-testing stations, a 65-foot climbing wall and more hands-on fun. Come let our friendly, knowledgeable staff help equip you for your next adventure!</longDescription><addressLine1>222 Yale Ave N</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Shopping Outdoor Adventure</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.619918</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.330413</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Misc</category><title>Nordstrom</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription></shortDescription><longDescription>Opened as a shoe store in 1901, this department store chain is now one of the nation's leading fashion retailers, offering fine apparel and accessories for everyone in the family. The stores are sleek and modern, mostly decorated in marble and wood. Shoes remain the specialty, with a huge selection that includes unusual sizes. Designer labels like Ralph Lauren, Donna Karan and Calvin Klein fill the clothing racks.</longDescription><addressLine1>1601 2nd Ave</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Shopping Shoes</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.610302</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.339771</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Food</category><title>Pike Place Fish Market</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>Located in Pike Place Market in Seattle, they have a crew of fish mongers who throw fish to entertain customers.</shortDescription><longDescription>We are the Seattle fresh fish company that everyone talks about. Besides offering only the best quality, freshest seafood, our dedication to having fun and creating excitement while we work makes us "world famous."</longDescription><addressLine1>86 Pike Place</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Food Eat Drink Fish</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.608833</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.34007</geo:long></geo:Point></item><item><category>Food</category><title>Purple Cafe and Wine Bar</title><imageURL>images/location_flower.png</imageURL><shortDescription>A multifaceted food and wine concept that merges casual sophistication with an upbeat metropolitan style.</shortDescription><longDescription>A multifaceted food and wine concept that merges casual sophistication with an upbeat metropolitan style. Purple features a global wine selection coupled with a menu that blends classic American styles, seasonal northwest ingredients and mediterranean themes.</longDescription><addressLine1>1225 4th Ave</addressLine1><addressLine2>Seattle, WA</addressLine2><date></date><keywords>Restaurant Drink Eat Food</keywords><recurrence>Daily</recurrence><geo:Point><geo:lat>47.607677</geo:lat><geo:long>-122.334392</geo:long></geo:Point></item></channel></rss>